 [
    {
      "answer": "delegation",
      "question": "Event, when an event handler is put only on a parent element and this element's child elements use this handler when the event happens"
    },
    {
      "answer": "capturing",
      "question": "Propagation of the event from a parent element to its child element"
    },
    {
      "answer": "element",
      "question": "Which base class for DOM elements offers navigation through elements and search methods like getElementsByTagName and querySelector"
    },
    {
      "answer": "array",
      "question": "Which internal (standard) JS structure is the most convenient and fastest to create a Stack"
    },       
    {
      "answer": "popover",
      "question": "A global attribute used to designate an element as a popover element is..."
    },       
    {
      "answer": "landscape",
      "question": "'orientation' parameter values in a media query are portrait and ..."
    },       
    {
      "answer": "enctype",
      "question": "What is attribute in <form> used for defines a type of sent data for a server"
    },       
    {
      "answer": "novalidate",
      "question": "What attribute for the <form> tag turns off built-in error messages and lets to add custom messages instead using JS"
    },       
    {
      "answer": "rebasing",
      "question": "How could you squash multiple commits together without using git merge --squash?"
    },       
    {
      "answer": "husky",
      "question": "Tool for automation of adding Git Hooks"
    }
]